(Howard:)Hang on.
(Penny:)Wait, you actually
think it's 2003?
(Sheldon:)No, just because
I'm living my life
(Sheldon:)like it was 12 years ago
doesn't mean I'm delusional.
(Sheldon:)And since it is 2003,
(Sheldon:)I don't know who you are,
(Sheldon:)so please exit the premises
(Sheldon:)before I call the police
on my stylish new flip phone.
(Penny:)Are you doing okay?
(Leonard:)I guess.
(Leonard:)I'm just, you know,
worried about Sheldon.
(Penny:)Well, come on,
he's a grown man in his 30s
(Penny:)pretending to be
a grown man in his 20s.
(Penny:)He's fine.
(Leonard:)I hope so.
(Penny:)What else can you do?
Move back in with him?
(Leonard:)No, of course not.
I-I just feel bad.
(Penny:)Well, so do I,
(Penny:)but don't you want to live
with your wife
(Penny:)and set the thermostat
(Penny:)to whatever you want
(Penny:)and have your body tell you
(Penny:)when it's time to go
to the bathroom,
(Penny:)you know, not a schedule slipped
(Penny:)underneath your door
every morning?
(Leonard:)I did like that he had
the weather on it.